

Karattukudy (H) Aruvappara P.O,



Meckappala, Kerala.683545



9207941032



anjanasuresh6798@gmail.com



ANJANA SURESH

PROFILE SUMMARY

Self-motivated, efficient, organized and goal-driven social worker who intended to work welfare, justice and empowerment of people and also enrich the family system. Also, my potentials will be fully discovered while working for the welfare dedicatedly and in gaining experience on the field.

EDUCATION

- [Bharata Mata College, Thrikkakara], [Master of Social Work], [B Grade], [2019-2021]
- [Mar Elias College, Kottappady], [Bachelor of Social Work], [A Grade], [2016-2019]
- [Boys Higher Secondary School Perumbavoor] [Humanities], [80%], [2014-2016]
- [Mar Elias Higher Secondary School Kottappady], [SSLC], [80%], [2014]

JOB EXPERIENCE

 Worked as Assistant Professor at Mar Elias College Kottappady from June 2022 to March 2023

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

- Worked as a volunteer at ADHISHAKTHI Summer camp at 2021
- Worked at Jeevika Migrant workers Movement Kalady from October 5th 2021 to September 10th 2021.
- Trainee at Navjeevan Trust Diocese of Rajkot, Gujarat from 1st January 2019 to 28th January 2019,28 days a part of internship by Mar Elias College, Kottappady.



 Internship Trainee at Ragagiri Out Reach, Ernakulam from 21st January 2017- 25th March 2017, as a part of the internship by Mar Elias College, Kottappady.

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

- A study on the effects of Covid 19 among women workers in unorganized sector with special reference to Ernakulam district" -2021
- Monograph "Rights of Children" 2020.
- "A study on the problem faced by women tea plantation workers in Idukki District.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of birth : 06/07/1998

Gender : Female

Marital status : Married

Nationality : Indian

Languages know : Malayalam and English

Skills : Leadership, Research,

Communication, Coordination, Public speaking,

Presentation, Poster making